//Questions array and question objects
var questionsArray = [
{
  question: "What does Todd Packers License plate say?",
  answerArray: ["PRVRT", "LOL69", "WLHUNG", "BOOB69"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, true, false],
  answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "Where does Ryan work after he gets fired from his corportate job?",
  answerArray: ["A Mall Kiosk", "A Bowling Alley", "A Fast Food Restaurant", "A Strip Club"],
  answerTrue: [false, true, false, false],
  answer: 1,
},
{
  question: "What item of clothing does Michael insist on having dry cleaned?",
  answerArray: ["Socks", "Ties", "Jeans", "Suit Jacket"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, true, false],
  answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "Who said,'I really should have a tweeter account?'",
  answerArray: ["Kevin", "Michael", "Creed", "Dwight"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, false, true],
  answer: 3,
},
{
    question: "What color shirts do the Scranton Branch employees wear in the episode 'Company Picnic'?",
    answerArray: ["Red", "Green", "Pink", "Orange"],
    answerTrue: [false, false, true, false],
    answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "What does Michael put in Toby's desk to frame him for drug posessoin?",
  answerArray: ["Ceaser Salad", "Frisee Salad", "Caprese Salad", "Spinach"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, true, false],
  answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "What does Andy say when he sees the topless picture of Jan taken in Jamaica?",
  answerArray: ["Boring. Call me if she rolls over.", "How do I get you out of that picture?", "Wait, is that Jan?", "Yea, Michael! You the man!"],
  answerTrue: [true, false, false, false],
  answer: 0,
},
{
  question: "What does Devon dress up as in Season 2 Halloween episode?",
  answerArray: ["A vampire", "A mummy", "A clown", "None of the Above"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, false, true],
  answer: 3,
},
{
  question: "What character does not appear in the pilot episode?",
  answerArray: ["Creed", "Kevin", "Kelly", "Ryan"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, true, false],
  answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "Who wins the bronze medal in the episode'Office Olympics?'",
  answerArray: ["Oscar", "Dwight", "Phyllis", "Jim"],
  answerTrue: [false, false, false, true],
  answer: 3,
},
];
